Howard S. Liebengood Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Senate Select Committee on Intelligence Files, 1950-1982 (Box 30-35)
  Correspondence, reports, executive orders, and legislation pertaining to the work of the Intelligence Committee. Almost all the material dates from the 1977-1978 debate over and ratification of the treaties.
  - Africa, 1978 (Box 30)
  - American Bar Association, Standing Committee on Law and National Security, 1980, undated
  - Angleton, James, 1976-1979, undated, (2 folders)
  - Association of Former Intelligence Officers, 1979-1980
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1975-1982, (4 folders)
  - Church of Scientology, 1978-1982
  - Computer security, 1977
  - Congressional Research Service, Library of Congress, 1975-1976, (2 folders)
  - Correspondence
    - Internal, 1976-1982, (2 folders)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1980, (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1978-1981
  - Cuba, 1978-1979
  - Derwinsky, Edward J., 1979-1980
  - Drugs, circa 1978
  - Ewing, Michael, 1975-1976, undated, (3 folders)
  - Executive orders on security and intelligence, 1978-1981
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1978-1981
  - Fontaine, Roger, 1978-1980
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1977-1980
  - Greece, undated
  - Helms, Richard, 1979-1981
  - Hougan, James, circa 1981-1982 (Box 32)
  - Hughes, Howard, 1970-1981
  - Intelligence Digest, 1980
  - Intelligence leaks, 1978-1981
  - Iran, 1978-1980
  - Israel, 1978-1979
  - Kennedy, John F., assassination, 1975-1978, undated
  - Kirkpatrick, Lyman, 1979-1980
  - Koreagate, 1977-1978
  - Legislation
    - Foreign Intelligence Act, 1976
    - National Intelligence Act
      - Drafts, 1978, (2 folders)
      - Memoranda, 1980
      - Notes, circa 1980
      - Outline, 1980
      - Miscellany, 1980
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1981, undated, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Libya, 1980-1981
  - Lorenz, Dirk, 1978-1982
  - Lorenz, Marita, 1950-1982, undated, (7 folders)
  - Middle East, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Notes, 1978-1982, undated
  - Paisley, John, 1979
  - Personnel, 1975-1982
  - Soviet Union, 1978-1982
  - Sternfield, Lawrence M., 1979-1981
  - Stewart, W. Donald, 1977-1980
  - Sturgis, Frank, 1977-1982, undated
  - Terpil, Frank, circa 1981
  - Terrorism, 1978-1980
  - Van Cleave, Steven, circa 1975-1981, undated
  - Vietnam, 1978-1979
  - Watergate, 1974-1982, undated, (2 folders)
  - Weaponry
    - Nuclear proliferation, 1972-1976, undated
    - Stealth technology, 1980, undated, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks II (SALT II), 1978-1979
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981, undated
- Watergate Committee Files, 1971-1982 (Box 35-38)
  Correspondence, reports, abstracts of interviews, compilations of Central Intelligence Agency documents, staff lists, newspaper clippings, legal papers, and notebooks.
  - Advance knowledge and double agent investigation (Box 35)
    - Interviews
      - Woolston-Smith, Arthur J., 1972-1974
      - Miscellany, 1973-1974
    - Memoranda, 1973-1975
    - Report, 1973
    - Miscellany, 1973
  - Anderson, Jack, 1973-1974
  - Arthur, Edward, 1972-1974
  - Central Intelligence Agency
    - Document classification, 1973-1974
    - Reports, 1974
    - Miscellany, undated
  - Correspondence
    - Culvahouse, A. B., 1975
    - Ervin, Sam J., 1977-1980
    - General, 1971-1974
    - Internal, 1973-1976
    - Liebengood, Howard S.
      - Memoranda, 1973-1975
      - Personal, 1973-1974
    - Public response, 1977-1979
    - Weis, Carl R., 1974-1975
  - Democratic party
    - Campaign finances, 1973
    - McGovern, George, presidential campaign dirty tricks investigation, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
    - Staff lists, undated
  - District of Columbia jail visitation records, 1972-1973
  - Ellsberg, Daniel, chronology of life, 1971
  - Ewing, Michael, information from, 1975-1976
  - Georgia presidential visit, 1972-1973
  - Haldeman, H. R., questions for, 1973
  - Howell, William Morgan, 1973
  - Hughes, Howard, and Global Marine, Inc., 1974
  - Intelligence Committee requests for documents, 1975
  - International Telephone and Telegraph, 1974, undated
  - Interviews and testimony
    - Bennett, Robert F., and Robert R. Mullen, 1974
    - Benz, William, 1973
    - Cantril, Susan Davis, 1973
    - Chajet, Elias, 1973-1974
    - Colson, Charles, 1975
    - Demotte, Clifton, 1974
    - Golden, James, 1973
    - Greigg, Stan, 1973
    - Haddad, William, 1973
    - Helms, Richard, 1973
    - Hunt, E. Howard, 1974
    - Kaiser, Edwin B., 1973-1974
    - Kelly, [?], 1973
    - Krogh, Egil ("Bud"), 1974
    - McGregor, Clark, 1973
    - Muller, Paul, 1973
    - O'Brien, Lawrence, 1973
    - Peloquin, R. [Robert D.?], 1974
    - Pico, [?], 1973
    - Sarhad, Ronald, 1973
    - Southwick, Thomas A., 1973
    - Stewart, John, 1973-1974
    - Young, David R., 1973
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
  - Legal papers
    - Affidavits, 1973
    - Motion for summary judgment, Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities v. Nixon, 1973
    - Research, 1973
    - Subpoenas, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973
  - Lundgren, John, physician of Richard M. Nixon, break-in of office, 1973
  - McGregor, Clark, 1972-1973
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Liebengood, Howard S., 1973-1975
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1978
  - Notebooks
    - Background material, 1973, (2 folders)
    - Dean, John, regarding
      - Ehrlichman, John, undated
      - Gray, L. Patrick, undated
      - Haldeman, H. R., undated
      - Magruder, Jeb Stuart, undated
      - Miscellaneous, undated
    - Personal
      - Untitled, 1973, (5 folders)
      - Vol. I, 1969-1974, (7 folders)
      - Vol. II, 1973-1974
        - Parts 1-3, (3 folders)
        - Parts 4-7, addition, (5 folders) (Box 38)
      - Vol. III, 1973-1974, undated, (7 folders)
  - Notes, circa 1973-circa 1976
  - November Group, 1972-1974
  - Photographs, 1973-1976, undated
  - Reports
    - Baker, Howard H., report regarding Central Intelligence Agency, 1974
    - Bennett, Robert F., regarding, 1974
    - Campaign practices, undated
    - Establishment of a joint intelligence oversight committee, 1974
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1972
    - "'Plumbers' and the Huston Plan," undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1979, undated
  - Republican National Convention
    - Disturbances, 1973
    - Dupont Plaza Hotel records, Miami, Fla., 1972-1973
  - Saunders, Frank, 1982
  - Sheridan, Walter, 1972-1974
  - Staff list, 1973
  - Telephone records, Frank Sturgis, 1973
  - Wilkes, Lloyd F., 1973-1980
  - Miscellany, 1974, undated
- Classified, 1971-1980 (Box CL 1)
  Correspondence, interviews, notebooks, reports, and testimony.
  Organized and described according to the series, folders, and boxes from which the items were removed.
  - Minority Leader's Office Files (Box CL 1)
    - Libya and Billy Carter
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Container 10)
  - Watergate Committee Files
    - Interviews and testimony
      - Bennett, Robert F., and Robert R. Mullen, 1974 (Container 36)
    - Notebooks
      - Personal
        - Vol. 1, 1971-1973 (Container 37)
        - Vol. 2, addition, 1973 (Container 38)
        - Vol. 3, 1973-1974 (Container 38)
    - Reports
      - Baker, Howard H., regarding Central Intelligence Agency, 1974 (Container 38)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1972 (Container 38)